本视频由Voice Memories小组译制 仅供学习交流使用
翻译·校对·时轴·后期 Mizore
Voice Memories招募小伙伴啦！
有意参与翻译、校对、时轴后期的同学请加审核群725940265 我们期待您的加入！
发之恋
3月
(发之恋)
人关注
关注
播放数
之前的视频
理发工具的链接
所有教程
只需要一些简单的工作
Just took a little bit of work
以及满满的爱
and a whole lot of love.
准备好了吗 来吧
Are you ready to do this? All right.
我们开始吧
Here we go.
看 是不是很简单
See? Now wasn't that easy?
只需要一些自信
All it takes is some confidence
以及开始的意愿
and a willingness to get started.
就算我不在你身边
And even though I'm not there,
我也会用这个视频来指导你
I'll guide you through this.
我想感谢我非常特别的助手
I want to thank my very special assistant,
我的女儿祖丽 像往常一样帮助我拍摄今天的vlog
my daughter Zuri, for helping me with today's vlog like always.
记住 前方的路或许崎岖
And remember, the road ahead might look rough,
然而只要付出些许努力 以及满满的爱
but you can make the journey with a little bit of work
总能走到终点
and a whole lot of love.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready to do this?
好的 我们开始吧
All right. Here we go.
首先 把这丛美丽的卷发
First you want to moisturize these beautiful thick curls
涂上护发素 这样打结的发丝就能理顺了
with a leave-in conditioner, which will also help detangle the kinks.
现在 把头发梳到两边 然后夹好
Now, part all your hair into sections and clip it away.
做得真棒
You're doing an amazing job.
太棒了 成功了
Yay! You did it!
是不是很有趣啊
That was so much fun.
我就知道你可以的
I knew you could do it.
Voice Memories小组 译制
翻译·校对·时轴·后期 Mizore
如果您喜欢这个作品 还请不要吝惜您的支持 感谢您的观看
温馨提示: Staff表也不要错过哦
没关系 没关系 一切都会好起来的
♪ Right, right ♪ gonna be all right ♪
因为已经好起来了
♪ 'Cause it's already ♪ all right ♪
没关系 没关系 一切都会顺利的
♪ Right, right ♪ gonna be all right ♪
因为已经很顺利了
♪ 'Cause it's already ♪ all right ♪
啊 欢乐时光 快乐时光
♪ Yeah ♪ happy days, happy days ♪
开心时光 愉悦时光
♪ Happy days, happy days ♪
只要做正确的事 这就是生活
♪ That's life ♪ when you do right ♪
十尺高 一里远
♪ Ten feet tall ♪ and a mile high ♪
欢乐时光 快乐时光
♪ Happy days, happy days ♪
开心时光 愉悦时光
啊 这就是生活 正确地生活
♪ Whoa, that's life ♪ when you live right ♪
一切都会是一碟小菜
♪ Finally got a piece ♪ of the pie, yeah ♪